Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Center Records UA188
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Center Records
1989 -- 2007
1972 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Center
UA188
13.65 Linear Feet 12 boxes and 1 oversized folder
25 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the LGBT Center, 2007-2018.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in five series: Office files; Promotional materials; Web crawls; 2018 accessions; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
In 1972 the Tufts Gay Community (TGC) organization was formed to provide a space for gay and bisexual people to meet and support one another and to educate the university community about gay related issues. Although the term "lesbian" was not included in the group name until 1981, the TGC's goal was to shed light on the issues facing the gay and lesbian community on campus. In 1980 the TGC established the first "drop-in center" on campus in Curtis Hall. By October 1987, the drop-in center was moved to Hayes House and In September of 1988, Donna Penn was hired as the first coordinator to increase programming and support services.
In 1992, with support from students, faculty and staff, Dean B. Knable established the first Lesbian Gay and Bisexual (LGB) Resource Center at Tufts in Lewis Hall and Heather Wishik replaced Donna Penn as administrator. After the holding of the first Pride on the Hill event in November 1992, the Center underwent a number of staff changes in the mid-1990s. This included the hiring of the first full-time director, Judith Brown in 1997.
In September 1998, the Tufts Rainbow House was established to provide safe housing for LGBT people on campus in light of the high number of bias incidents that occurred in residence halls. In January 2003 Dona Yarbrough was hired as the LGBT Center Director and began to push for a housing policy that would accommodate transgender students at Tufts. In the fall of 2004, Yarbrough's Transgender Housing Policy was adopted by Residential Life and the Center also began organizing its Queer Peer mentoring program. Upon the suggestion of Yarbrough, the administration accepted a revision to Tufts University non-discrimination policy by adding gender identity and expression in the fall of 2005. From 1997 until the present, the LGBT Center has organized annual and statewide Safe Colleges Conferences, originally called "Sound Mind, Sound Body, Sound Off." The conferences include a keynote speaker and workshops created by staff and organizations, both from campus and off-campus.
Under the umbrella of the Dean of Students, the LGBT Center is part of the Group of Six, which includes: Women's Center, Africana Center, Latino Center, Asian American Center, and the International Center.
Related Materials
International Center records, 1953-2012. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Asian American Center Records, 1980 -- 2017. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
The collection is composed of office records, newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, slides, event posters, publications, reports, web crawls, digital media, and promotional materials, including buttons, magnets, pins, stickers, t-shirts, a blanket, and graduation tassels, related to the history and activities of the Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Center at Tufts University. The bulk of the material dates from 1989 to 2007. The materials reflect the organization's efforts to promote LGBT rights, to raise awareness about issues facing this community, and to provide a safe space for LGBT people at Tufts. Photographs in the collection are restricted for 75 years to protect the privacy of individuals depicted in the photos.
Gay and lesbian rights; Transgender people; Transgender people--identity; Lesbian Gay and Bisexual Resource Center; Queer Peers mentoring program; Safe Colleges Conference; Ballou Hall; Lewis Hall; Discrimination in higher education; Anti-LGBT bias; Student Affairs and Services; Student life; Student activities; Student activism; Health and Safety
- Office files, 1972 -- 2011; UA188.001; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Center records, 1980–2012: Office files 1980-2012 Contains office records, photographs, event information, newspaper clippings, newsletters, digital objects, and educational materials. The bulk of the material spans from 1989-2007. Materials from Tufts faculty members Jonathan Strong and Jeanne Penvenne related to the LGBT Faculty Staff Caucus were incorporated into this series. The office files provide a window into LGBT rights activism and events held at Tufts. There are records and newspaper articles documenting the students' opposition in the early 2000s to actions taken by the Tufts Christian Fellowship to prevent a lesbian student member from taking a leadership position in their organization. This series also contains research files compiled during the Summer Scholars award that led to the creation of the Tufts Queer History Project website by Tufts student Elena Mead.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation.
  - Alumni Names - old, 2003 -- 2006; UA188.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Argus - Group of 6, 2001; UA188.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Argus - Group of 6, 2001; UA188.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Center Plans, 1994 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Co-Ed Housing, 2001; UA188.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Educational Materials, 2003 -- 2005; UA188.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Evals, 2004 -- 2005; UA188.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Funding, 2004 -- 2005; UA188.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Guess the Straight Person, 2011; UA188.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Hate Crimes Information, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 5, 1997 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Hate Crimes Legislation, binder, folder 2 of 5, 1998 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Hate Crimes Statistics, binder, folder 3 of 5, 1991 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Hate Crimes Matthew Shepherd, binder, folder 4 of 5, 1998 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Hate Crimes, Tufts, binder, folder 5 of 5, 1996 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Keynote, 1995 -- 2005; UA188.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - LGB Resource Center, 1997 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Center, 2000 -- 2002; UA188.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Center, 2002 -- 2003; UA188.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Center, 2003 -- 2004; UA188.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Center Posterboard, 2006; UA188.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Fac-Staff, 1997 -- 2001; UA188.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty/Staff Caucus, 1993 -- 1994; UA188.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty/Staff Caucus, 1992 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty-Staff Caucus Documents, 1990 -- 1999; UA188.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty/Staff Caucus - Penvenne, Jeanne, 1997 -- 2011; UA188.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty/Staff Caucus - Strong, Jonathan, folder 1 of 2, 1992 -- 2004; UA188.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Faculty/Staff Caucus - Strong, Jonathan, folder 2 of 2, 2000; UA188.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 14, 1999; UA188.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, pre-1980, binder, folder 2 of 14, 1972; UA188.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 3 of 14, 1980; UA188.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 4 of 14, 1981; UA188.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 5 of 14, 1982; UA188.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 6 of 14, 1983; UA188.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 7 of 14, 1984; UA188.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 8 of 14, 1985; UA188.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 9 of 14, 1986; UA188.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 10 of 14, 1987; UA188.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 11 of 14, 1988; UA188.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 12 of 14, 1989; UA188.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 13 of 14, 1990; UA188.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, binder, folder 14 of 14, 1991; UA188.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 12, 1999; UA188.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 2 of 12, 1992; UA188.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 3 of 12, 1993; UA188.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 4 of 12, 1994; UA188.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 5 of 12, 1995; UA188.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 6 of 12, 1996; UA188.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 7 of 12, 1997; UA188.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 8 of 12, 1998; UA188.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 9 of 12, 1999; UA188.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 10 of 12, 2000; UA188.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 11 of 12, 2000; UA188.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Issues in Campus Publications, front matter, binder, folder 12 of 12, 2001; UA188.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - Literary Magazine - Queer, 1997 -- 1998; UA188.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, Bi Issues, binder, folder 1 of 5, 1996 -- 1997; UA188.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, Health Issues, binder, folder 2 of 5, 1996 -- 1997; UA188.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, Pride on Hill, binder, folder 3 of 5, 1993 -- 1994; UA188.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, Religious, binder, folder 4 of 5, 1996 -- 1997; UA188.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, binder, folder 5 of 5, 1996 -- 1997; UA188.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - Past Events, binder, folder 1 of 1, 2003; UA188.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Photos from LGBTQ Bulletin Board, 1989 -- 2003; UA188.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Photos - TLGBC Past, folder 1 of 4, 1989 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - Photos - TLGBC Past, folder 2 of 4, 1989 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - Photos - TLGBC Past, folder 3 of 4, 1989 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - Photos - TLGBC Past, folder 4 of 4, 1989 -- 2000; UA188.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - Photos - TLGBC Rally for Action - Ballou Hall, folder 1 of 5, 1992; UA188.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Photos - TLGBC Rally for Action - Ballou Hall, folder 2 of 5, 1992; UA188.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Photos - TLGBC Rally for Action - Ballou Hall, folder 3 of 5, 1992; UA188.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Photos - TLGBC Rally for Action - Ballou Hall, folder 4 of 5, 1992; UA188.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Photos - TLGBC Rally for Action - Ballou Hall, folder 5 of 5, 1992; UA188.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Photos - Tufts Past, folder 1 of 2, 1995 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Photos - Tufts Past, folder 2 of 2, 1995 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Photos - Unlabeled, 1998 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Publicity, 2004; UA188.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Program, 2003 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Q Tips - Past, 1997 -- 2001; UA188.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Queer Peers, binder, folder 1 of 1, 2005 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Queer Students of Color and Allies, 2006; UA188.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Safe Colleges, 2000; UA188.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Safe Colleges, 2004 -- 2006; UA188.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Safe Colleges 2003, UA188.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Safe Colleges Conference Materials, 2003 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - SCC Press and Procedures, 2005; UA188.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - SCC Programs, 2003 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Senior Class Surveys, 1992; UA188.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Task Force on Race, 1997 -- 1999; UA188.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Task Force Reports, 1993 -- 1995; UA188.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - TCF, 1985 -- 2000; UA188.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - TCF Discrimination Case Articles, 2000 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Trans Accounts of Bias, 2005; UA188.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Trans Articles About Institutional Issues, 2003 -- 2005; UA188.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Trans Book/Video Recommendations, 2005; UA188.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Trans Chronicle Discrim. Article, 2005; UA188.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Trans Day of Remembrance, 2004; UA188.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Trans Gender Aptitude Test, 2005; UA188.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Trans History, 2004; UA188.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Trans Issue Statement, 2005; UA188.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Trans Issue Statement Copies, 2005; UA188.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Trans Newspaper Articles, 2002 -- 2004; UA188.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Trans Samuel Lurie Materials, 2005; UA188.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Trans Speakers/Workshops, 2005; UA188.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Trans Trans and Non-discrim Workshop, 2005; UA188.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Trans TransGender Theory, 2004; UA188.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Transgressing Binaries, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 2, 2002; UA188.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Transgressing Binaries, binder, folder 2 of 2, 2002; UA188.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Triangle Talk binder, 2006; UA188.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGB Resource Center Programming, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 2, 1997 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGB Resource Center Programming, binder, folder 2 of 2, 1997 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGBT and Women's Center Pamphlets, 2000 -- 2007; UA188.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGBT Center Photographs, 2005; UA188.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGBT Events, 2005; UA188.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Tufts LGBT History, 1994 -- 2003; UA188.001.003.00001 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts LGBT History, 1994 -- 2003; UA188.001.003.00002 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts LGBT History, 1994 -- 1998; UA188.001.003.00003 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts LGBT History, 1992 -- 1994; UA188.001.003.00004 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts LGBT History, 1994 -- 1999; UA188.001.003.00005 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Students Against Discrimination, 2000; UA188.001.003.00006 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Task Force Reports, front matter, binder, folder 1 of 4, 1994 -- 1997; UA188.001.003.00007 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Task Force Reports, LGB, binder, folder 2 of 4, 1993 -- 1994; UA188.001.003.00008 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Task Force Reports, ROTC, binder, folder 3 of 4, 1997; UA188.001.003.00009 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Task Force Reports, Race, binder, folder 4 of 4, 1997; UA188.001.003.00010 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Vision Statement, 1994; UA188.001.003.00011 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
- Promotional materials, 1989 -- 2012; UA188.002; 4.1 Linear Feet
  This series contains promotional materials and ephemera. There are posters and rally signs from events held by the LGBT community at Tufts during the 2000s. This series also contains buttons from Pride on the Hill and the Tufts Lebsian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Center.
  Open for research.
  - LGBT Event and Safety Posters, 2012; UA188.002.003.00012 (Box Shared 74)
  - National Coming Out Day Stickers, undated, 1989 -- 2012; UA188.002.003.00013 (Box UA188 Shared 1)
  - Posters, 1989 -- 2012; UA188.002.003.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 5)
  - Pride on the Hill button magnets, 1992; UA188.002.003.00015 (Box Shared 16)
  - Straight But Not Narrow buttons, 1989 -- 2012; UA188.002.003.00016 (Box Shared 16)
  - Tufts Rainbow buttons, 1992; UA188.002.003.00017 (Box Shared 16)
  - Tufts Rainbow tassle, 1989 -- 2012; UA188.002.003.00018 (Box Shared 16)
  - Tufts Undergraduate Orientation Peer Leader T-Shirt, 2011; UA188.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2019; UA188.003; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Center at Tufts University website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Center at Tufts University, 2015 -- 2020; UA188.003.00001; Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Center
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
- 2018 accessions, circa 2003 -- 2018; UA188.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged in received order.
  This series is open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the LGBT Center, 2018, accession UA-2019-044.
  This series contains photographs of events related to the LGBT Center, and promotional pins and stickers, t-shirts, and a blanket.
  - Coming Out Day, 2003 -- 2009; UA188.004.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Team Q Retreat, 2009 -- 2013; UA188.004.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bolles House BBQ, 2011; UA188.004.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Pins and stickers, circa 2010 -- 2018; UA188.004.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LGBT Center t-shirts, circa 2010 -- 2018; UA188.004.004.00005; 0.5 Linear Feet (Box 4)
    Four different t-shirts promoting the LGBT Center and related events.
  - LGBT Center blanket, circa 2010 -- 2018; UA188.004.004.00006; 0.5 Linear Feet (Box 4)
    One blanket promoting the LGBT Center.
- Additional accessions, 1989 -- 2015; 2006 -- 2015; UA188.005
  - Slides, 1989 -- 2012; UA188-004 (Box data_value_missing_4e38412b28a94830cca63ef455f650ae, Box 1)
    Contains a box of slides copyrighted by the photographer Keitaro Yoshioka.
  - Coming out day, 2007-10-17; UA188-005
  - TQHP Site, 2007-08-09; UA188-006
    The Tufts Queer History Project started as a Tufts Summer Scholars Research Project in 2006. Tufts student Elena Mead was awarded the research scholar grant. She worked with Dona Yarbrough, director of the LGBT Center at the time, on TQHP, which culminated in the creation of a website. The TQHP website sought to document the history of the LGBT community at Tufts from the late 1960s into the 2000s.
  - TQHP Site, 2007-06-20; UA188-007
  - TQHP Site, 2007-04-10; UA188-008
  - Updates, 2007-03-28; UA188-009
  - TQHP, 2007-01-11; UA188-011
  - TQHP Research Symposium, 2007-03-09; UA188-012
  - TQHP, 2007-01-11; UA188-013
  - TQHP, 2006-11-20; UA188-014
  - TQHP, 2006-11-14; UA188-015
  - TQHP, 2006-11-09; UA188-016
  - TQHP, 2006-11-02; UA188-017
  - TQHP v_2, 2006-11-02; UA188-018
  - TQHP v_1, 2006-11-02; UA188-019
  - TQHP, 2006-11-01; UA188-020
  - TQHP, 2006-10-31; UA188-021
  - TQHP, 2006-10-30; UA188-022
  - TQHP am, 2006-10-30; UA188-023
  - Summer Scholar Presentation, 2007; UA188-024
    Created in 2003, the Summer Scholars program is an initiative of Tufts University that awards research apprenticeships to undergraduate students.
  - Summer Scholars, 2007; UA188-025
  - Film Archive, 2007-08; UA188-026
  - GI Joe, 2007; UA188-027
  - Tufts Students Against Discrimination (TSAD) files, 2000; UA188-028; Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Center; Barry, Dan
    In response to the homophobia claim that was made in April 2000 as well as the unsuccessful attempt to change the non-discrimination policy, a group called Tufts Students Against Discrimination (TSAD) was formed to fight against discrimination at Tufts. In the beginning of fall of 2000, the students organized a sit-in at the Tufts Admissions Building, called Bendetson Hall. They took over the building until the language in the non-discrimination policy better fit the needs of all students regardless of their belief system. The action was successful and very visible. The students took over the building for two days and one night and were met by significant administrative action on revising the policy.The folder named "TSAD" contains all the digital documents pertaining to the TSAD movement and sit-in, except for the aforementioned two.The folder named "TSAD Archive Scans" contains Dan Barry's scans of physical documents from that time, including flyers from campus and newspaper clippings. The folder named "E-mail" is as complete a record as Dan could generate of the correspondence between TSAD members, including messages on the group's Listserv and personal, TSAD-related correspondence that Dan was involved in.
  - TSAD oral history interview with Dan Barry, 2009; UA188-029
    This digital object contains a video of a Tufts Students Against Discrimination (TSAD) oral history interview with Tufts graduate, Dan Barry. The interview was conducted by Elena Mead.
    Barry, Dan
  - TQHP Final Four, 2006-11-02; UA188-030
    This digital object contains bagged files from a DVD created for the Tufts Queer History Project.
  - TQHP Films, 2007; UA188-031
  - LGBT Center T-shirt, 1989 -- 1999; UA188-032 (Box data_value_missing_5fc291088f914de1e96e9b3322cd4d13, Box 2)
  - Office files and newsletters, 1992 -- 2014; UA188-033 (Box data_value_missing_68c006714ef8f4def992b0ea6b56e9f9, Box 3)
  - Posters, 1998 -- 2013; UA188-034 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 4)
  - Office files, 1992 -- 2015; UA188-035 (Box data_value_missing_56a3bdb5ad4f8666ad485a4fd255fba0, Box 4)
  - Office files, 1992 -- 2015; UA188-036 (Box data_value_missing_56a3bdb5ad4f8666ad485a4fd255fba0, Box 5)